<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-10-31T07:37:48+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">dizzy kitchen</title><subtitle>A fun cooking/recipies website</subtitle><author><name>Diana Zhang</name><email>contact@dizzydizzykitchen.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">sweet potato fries</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/sides/western/2018/10/15/sweet-potato-fries/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="sweet potato fries" /><published>2018-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-10-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/sides/western/2018/10/15/sweet-potato-fries</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/sides/western/2018/10/15/sweet-potato-fries/">&lt;p&gt;Sweet potato fries has been the ultimate childhood favorite of mine. There was this shop basically walking distance from my house that sold boba and asian quick eats. I remember every time I went there, I would make a huge deal out of it. My favorite favorite favorite thing to order there was their sweet potato fries and crispy chicken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, I digress. This dish is super easy to make. It took no time at all and plus, it’s way healthier than having deep friend potatoes. Not only are sweet potatoes a good source of fiber, but they also very low in saturated fat and cholesterol. Basically they are root vegetable that are filled with nutrients, so you won’t feel guilty when consuming it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For next time, I would probably line my pan with aluminum foil or parchment paper. These will stick. Believe me, I learned that the hard way. I will also play with the flavors a little more by adding some garlic powder or paprika. Recently, my dad gifted me worcestershire pepper. I don’t know why, but I’m just not going to ask. Apparently, its some type of seasoning for barbecues, but I’m sure it will taste great with these sweet potatoes. I wanted to keep it simple for this round, but I will definitely spice it up next time. No pun intended!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;840&quot; height=&quot;560&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/QH2-TGUlwu4&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name>Diana Zhang</name><email>contact@dizzydizzykitchen.com</email></author><summary type="html">Sweet potato fries has been the ultimate childhood favorite of mine. There was this shop basically walking distance from my house that sold boba and asian quick eats. I remember every time I went there, I would make a huge deal out of it. My favorite favorite favorite thing to order there was their sweet potato fries and crispy chicken.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">snow-skin mooncakes</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/desserts/asian/2018/10/07/snow-skin-mooncakes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="snow-skin mooncakes" /><published>2018-10-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-10-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/desserts/asian/2018/10/07/snow-skin-mooncakes</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/desserts/asian/2018/10/07/snow-skin-mooncakes/">&lt;p&gt;Eating mooncake during the mid-autumn festival has always been a Chinese family tradition. I think&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This particular type of mooncake is famous to the Guangzhou area or at least the southern part of China. It’s not like the traditional mooncake thats baked and usually filled with some type of salted duck egg yolk. This mooncake, with the amount of glutinous flour used, almost takes like a Japanese mochi. And when frozen, mochi ice cream! Now who doesn’t love that? All in all, it’s sweet, subtly creamy, and just a wonderful treat to share with friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How would I alter this for next time? Hmm… I want to explore the different flavors that I can make with this dish. I have made a separate attempt at making a matcha-skinned, ube-filled mooncake and not going to lie, that was pretty delicious too. Anyways, if you have the time, try out this recipe! It’s the mid-autumn festival after all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;840&quot; height=&quot;560&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/QH2-TGUlwu4&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name>Diana Zhang</name><email>contact@dizzydizzykitchen.com</email></author><summary type="html">Eating mooncake during the mid-autumn festival has always been a Chinese family tradition. I think</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">boba milk tea</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/drinks/asian/2018/09/20/boba-milk-tea/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="boba milk tea" /><published>2018-09-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-09-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/drinks/asian/2018/09/20/boba-milk-tea</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/drinks/asian/2018/09/20/boba-milk-tea/">&lt;p&gt;Boba Milk Tea has always been a childhood favorite of mine; however, it can get a little expensive. With this recipe,
you can make a ton at a very low price. This recipe is super fun to make with family or with friends and because you are working with dough, don’t be afraid to play around and make your own shapes! Plus, hand-making the tapioca pearls is a good alternative because then you know exactly what you are putting in your body. There’s nothing processed, nothing faked. This is just about as natural as you can get with a drink like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this recipe, you can really make it your own. You can swap out the matcha powder for strawberry ice cream or mango puree. You can even try green tea instead of black tea. Using almond or cashew milk instead of regular milk is super delicious as well!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What will I do better next time? My goal would probably be to make the boba way smaller. As you can from the video, I made some thicc balls, thicc enough I could barely get them up the straw. Oh well! We’re all still on a learning curve right? I’d also like to explore into the realm of Hong Kong milk teas. I recently came back from Hong Kong and apparently there is this super famous shop named Lan Fong Yuen on Hong Kong Island that will filter your tea through a woman’s stocking! Because its such a fine sieve, the tea will come out silky smooth. They also will add in some evaporated milk I believe. Stay tuned for a new recipe soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;840&quot; height=&quot;560&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/QH2-TGUlwu4&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name>Diana Zhang</name><email>contact@dizzydizzykitchen.com</email></author><summary type="html">Boba Milk Tea has always been a childhood favorite of mine; however, it can get a little expensive. With this recipe, you can make a ton at a very low price. This recipe is super fun to make with family or with friends and because you are working with dough, don’t be afraid to play around and make your own shapes! Plus, hand-making the tapioca pearls is a good alternative because then you know exactly what you are putting in your body. There’s nothing processed, nothing faked. This is just about as natural as you can get with a drink like this.</summary></entry></feed>